<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>event-driven automation on StackStorm</title><link>https://stackstorm.github.io/stackstorm.com/tags/event-driven-automation/</link><description>Recent content in event-driven automation on StackStorm</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 13:52:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://stackstorm.github.io/stackstorm.com/tags/event-driven-automation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Serverless’ Event Gateway explained for StackStorm users</title><link>https://stackstorm.github.io/stackstorm.com/2017/10/10/event-grid-event-gateway-explained-part2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 13:52:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stackstorm.github.io/stackstorm.com/2017/10/10/event-grid-event-gateway-explained-part2/</guid><description>&lt;p>October 10, 2017&lt;br>
&lt;em>by &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->Dmitri Zimine&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In &lt;a href="https://stackstorm.com/2017/10/05/event-grid-event-gateway-explained-part1/">Part 1&lt;/a> of the series, I shared my excitement with two new event-driven systems introduced last month: &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->Event Grid&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --> from Microsoft Azure and &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->Event Gateway&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --> from &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->Serverless.com&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->, and posted some observations on Event Grid.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Before we continue with Event Gateway, let’s bring the “terminology normalization” from &lt;a href="https://stackstorm.com/2017/10/05/event-grid-event-gateway-explained-part1/">Part 1&lt;/a>. In the table below StackStorm terms are used as as a reference point for our blog’s regular readers, along with a short explanation of their meaning for the guests.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Innovation at Dimension Data: Accelerating Innovation and Digital Transformation with StackStorm Event Driven Automation</title><link>https://stackstorm.github.io/stackstorm.com/2017/01/24/innovation-at-dimension-data-event-driven-automation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 16:36:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stackstorm.github.io/stackstorm.com/2017/01/24/innovation-at-dimension-data-event-driven-automation/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>Jan 24, 2017&lt;/strong>&lt;br>
&lt;em>by Dana Christensen&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="part-1-of-3">Part 1 of 3&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>At DevOps Enterprise Summit 2016, DevOps leaders like Target, American Airlines, Disney, and Quicken Loans spoke of the importance of managing/optimizing operations, addressing technical debt, eliminating silos, collaboration, and the importance of open source and community to drive innovation. I was especially struck by &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->Jason Cox of Disney&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->, who stressed the importance of “creating a culture of courage” where teams are encouraged to be curious, to experiment, explore and embrace change across process, roles, and technology-all for the purpose of enabling meaningful work.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>It turns out that these themes are being talked about not only by these large Enterprise DevOps leaders. These themes are being repeated in conversations around the globe with IT leaders who are looking to leverage DevOps practices to successfully drive innovation and digital transformation.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Anthony Shaw, Group Director of Innovation and Technical Talent at &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->Dimension Data&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --> has seen this first hand. Anthony not only leads innovation efforts within Dimension Data-but he also travels the world speaking with customers about their business priorities, their Digital Transformation goals, and how the innovative use of technology, organizational structure, community, and transforming day to day operational practices can accelerate their Digital Transformation journey.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Unleash the power of IoT with Event-Driven Automation (ST2 &amp; BWC @ SuperComputing16)</title><link>https://stackstorm.github.io/stackstorm.com/2016/11/14/iot-event-driven-automation-supercomputing16/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 19:09:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stackstorm.github.io/stackstorm.com/2016/11/14/iot-event-driven-automation-supercomputing16/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>By Chip Copper, PhD;&lt;/strong> Principal Technology Evangelist, Brocade&lt;br>
&lt;em>Nov 14, 2016&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The pattern is the same: “I can’t because we don’t…”, “But we are also…”, “Can I …”, and finally “How do I get it?”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We’re demonstrating Brocade Workflow Composer (BWC), powered by &lt;a href="http://stackstorm.com">StackStorm&lt;/a>, at &lt;a href="http://www.brocade.com/en/about-us/events/sc16.html">SuperComputing16&lt;/a> in Salt Lake City. When you stop by booth 1131, we will give you a token of our appreciation. It’s an NodeMCU microcontroller. It’s pretty cool – WiFi built in, ARM microcontroller, lots of GPIO pins, and it can easily be programmed using the freely-available Arduino IDE. It gets you into the world of IoT quickly and easily, and it’s a lot of fun! Bonus!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But there is a catch – you have to watch a demo to get it.&lt;/p>
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --></description></item><item><title>StackStorm at OpenStack Barcelona</title><link>https://stackstorm.github.io/stackstorm.com/2016/11/03/stackstorm-at-openstack-barcelona/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 08:09:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stackstorm.github.io/stackstorm.com/2016/11/03/stackstorm-at-openstack-barcelona/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>Nov 01, 2016&lt;/strong>&lt;br>
&lt;em>by Dmitri Zimine&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Lights flashing at the StackStorm-Brocade booth made event-driven automation feel real with the IoT demo entertaining enterprise and DevOps crowds alike. Mirantis’ talk about auto-healing Symantec OpenStack cloud with StackStorm sparkled hallway conversations about auto-remediation. Our guerrilla hacking challenge was success, unveiled that the best hackers are all co-located…(guess where, anyone?)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Read on for details.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Auto-Remediation for Real: Self-Healing Clouds and Auto-Remediation as a Service</title><link>https://stackstorm.github.io/stackstorm.com/2016/10/27/auto-remediation-for-real-self-healing-clouds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 18:58:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stackstorm.github.io/stackstorm.com/2016/10/27/auto-remediation-for-real-self-healing-clouds/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>Oct 27, 2016&lt;/strong>&lt;br>
&lt;em>by Dana Christensen&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>What do companies like eBay, VMware, Facebook, Netflix, Mirantis, Verizon, Infosys, Cisco, Dell, LinkedIn, and Apple have in common?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>They all attended the &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->Auto-Remediation and Event-Driven Automation MeetUp&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --> on Oct. 20th hosted by the StackStorm team at Brocade in San Jose.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The topic for the evening was “Remediation For Real” and both Mirantis and Netflix provided excellent overviews and demonstrations of how auto-remediation is helping to address business issues and increase their engineers’ productivity (and sleeptime!).&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>OpenStack Summit Barcelona Preview: Resiliency, High Availability, Adaptability, and Self-Healing with StackStorm Event-Driven Automation</title><link>https://stackstorm.github.io/stackstorm.com/2016/10/12/openstack-summit-barcelona-preview/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 02:50:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stackstorm.github.io/stackstorm.com/2016/10/12/openstack-summit-barcelona-preview/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="stackstorm-at-openstack-summit-highlights">StackStorm at OpenStack Summit Highlights:&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Booth: B34 (You’ll find us in the Brocade Booth)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->StackStorm Theater Presentation&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->: StackStorm and OpenStack: Two Practical Cases for Event Driven Automation; Wed 26 11:20am-11:45am, &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->P0 – Marketplace Theater&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Mirantis Session: &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->Sleep Better at Night: OpenStack Cloud Auto­-Healing&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Design Summit: Mistral Working Sessions&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --></description></item></channel></rss>